const jquizData = [{
    Question:
        'What is a correct syntax to output "Hello World" in Java?',
    Options: [
        'Console.WriteLine("Hello World");',
        'System.out.println("Hello World");',
        'echo("Hello World");',
        'print ("Hello World");',],
    Correct: 1,
},
{
    Question:
        'Java is short for "JavaScript".',
    Options: [
        "Don't know",
        'True',
        'False ',
        'None',],
    Correct: 2,
},
{
    Question:
        'How do you insert COMMENTS in Java code?',
    Options: [
        '/* This is a comment',
        '// This is a comment  ',
        '# This is a comment',
        "Don't know",],
    Correct: 1,
},
{
    Question:
        'Which data type is used to create a variable that should store text?',
    Options: [
        'Txt ',
        'String',
        'myString',
        'string',],
    Correct: 1,
},
{
    Question:
        'How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5?',
    Options: [
        'float x = 5; ',
        'x = 5;',
        'int x = 5;',
        'num x = 5',],
    Correct: 2,
},
{
    Question:
        'How do you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?',
    Options: [
        'x = 2.8f;',
        'float x = 2.8f;',
        'int x = 2.8f;',
        'byte x = 2.8f',],
    Correct: 1
},
{
    Question:
        'Which method can be used to find the length of a string?',
    Options: [
        'getSize()',
        'len()',
        'getLength()',
        'length()   ',],
    Correct: 3,
},
{
    Question:
        'Which operator is used to add together two values?',
    Options: [
        'The & sign',
        'The * sign',
        'The + sign  ',
        'The / sign ',],
    Correct: 2,
},
{
    Question:
        'The value of a string variable can be surrounded by single quotes.',
    Options: [
        "Don't know",
        'False   ',
        'True',
        'None',],
    Correct: 1,
},
{
    Question:
        'Which method can be used to return a string in upper case letters?',
    Options: [
        'upperCase()',
        'touppercase()',
        'toUpperCase()  ',
        'tuc()',],
    Correct: 2,
},
{
    Question:
        'Which operator can be used to compare two values?',
    Options: [
        '=    ',
        '><',
        '<>',
        '==  ',],
    Correct: 3,
},
{
    Question:
        'To declare an array in Java, define the variable type with:',
    Options: [
        '{} ',
        '()',
        '[]  ',
        'None',],
    Correct: 2,
},
{
    Question:
        'Array indexes start with:',
    Options: [
        "Don't know",
        '0  ',
        '1',
        'None',],
    Correct: 1,
},
{
    Question:
        'How do you create a method in Java?',
    Options: [
        'methodName() ',
        'methodName.',
        '(methodName)',
        'methodName[]',],
    Correct: 0,
},
{
    Question:
        'How do you call a method in Java?',
    Options: [
        'methodName;     ',
        'methodName();  ',
        'methodName[];',
        '(methodName);',],
    Correct: 1,
},
{
    Question:
        'Which keyword is used to create a class in Java?',
    Options: [
        'class    ',
        'class()',
        'className',
        'MyClass',],
    Correct: 0,
},
{
    Question:
        'What is the correct way to create an object called myObj of MyClass?',
    Options: [
        'new myObj = MyClass();   ',
        'class myObj = new MyClass();',
        'MyClass myObj = new MyClass(); ',
        'class MyClass = new myObj();',],
    Correct: 2,
},
{
    Question:
        'In Java, it is possible to inherit attributes and methods from one class to another.',
    Options: [
        "Don't Know ",
        'False    ',
        'True   ',
        'None',],
    Correct: 2,
},
{
    Question:
        'Which method can be used to find the highest value of x and y?',
    Options: [
        'Math.max(x,y)     ',
        'Math.largest(x,y)',
        'Math.maximum(x,y)',
        'Math.maxNum(x,y)',],
    Correct: 0,
},
{
    Question:
        'Which operator is used to multiply numbers?',
    Options: [
        '#  ',
        '%',
        '*   ',
        'x',],
    Correct: 2,
},
{
    Question:
        'Which keyword is used to import a package from the Java API library?',
    Options: [
        'import',
        'lib',
        'package',
        'getlib',],
    Correct: 0,
},
{
    Question:
        'How do you start writing an if statement in Java?',
    Options: [
        'if x > y then:',
        'if (x > y) ',
        'if x > y:',
        'None',],
    Correct: 2,
},
{
    Question:
        'How do you start writing a while loop in Java?',
    Options: [
        'while x > y {    ',
        'while (x > y)  ',
        'x > y while {',
        'while x > y:',],
    Correct: 1,
},
{
    Question:
        'Which keyword is used to return a value inside a method?',
    Options: [
        'return',
        'get',
        'void',
        'break',],
    Correct: 0,
},
{
    Question:
        'Which statement is used to stop a loop?',
    Options: [
        'exit  ',
        'stop',
        'return',
        'break ',],
    Correct: 3,
}]